[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 47?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "6936.26",
      "options": [
        "6934.76",
        "6939.26",
        "6937.76",
        "6936.26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 63?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "12462.66",
      "options": [
        "12464.16",
        "12465.66",
        "12461.16",
        "12462.66"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 64?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "12861.44",
      "options": [
        "12862.94",
        "12859.94",
        "12864.44",
        "12861.44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 62?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "12070.16",
      "options": [
        "12071.66",
        "12068.66",
        "12073.16",
        "12070.16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 4?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "50.24",
      "options": [
        "51.74",
        "53.24",
        "48.74",
        "50.24"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 53?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "8820.26",
      "options": [
        "8818.76",
        "8823.26",
        "8821.76",
        "8820.26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 65?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "13266.5",
      "options": [
        "13265.0",
        "13268.0",
        "13269.5",
        "13266.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 49?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "7539.14",
      "options": [
        "7537.64",
        "7539.14",
        "7542.14",
        "7540.64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 76?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "18136.64",
      "options": [
        "18138.14",
        "18139.64",
        "18136.64",
        "18135.14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 14?(Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "615.44",
      "options": [
        "618.44",
        "616.94",
        "613.94",
        "615.44"
      ]
    }
]